ok so where does integration by parts come from well it comes from the product
product or if you want to sound fancy for
if I have two functions f and G
I multiply then and then I differentiate and thanks G Prime is f prime plus Jeep
which means that sgps X G prime = f x g
prime - prime X G and if I integrate both sides
then I end up with the integration by parts which is best
the XX if the functions of x = f f x g minor
f-prime x GTX ok this is the version of indefinite integrals
you can have a definite into love versions where you put the limits of integration
let me spell it out so this is the definite in
alright so let's do a couple of eggs
so the first thing
so I suppose I want to integrate x squared sign x
so this would solve so this would be
this gives the solution to DY
x = x squared sign x ok so we need to be patient by parts you have
which one is f and which ones now clearly I would like to decrease the power here I know I can never